Tsubaki
Kirishima said what?
That he went to Osaka to see you
when he was 12 years old.
He did say he didn't manage
to catch you, though.
Why would he do that?
Good question.
Maybe he already liked you back then?
Well, he originally hoped I was a
dumb, spoiled bitch for some reason.
I'm not even sure he likes me for real.
What do you mean?
I get the feeling that if I actually did
like him, he'd lose all interest in me.
It's less that he likes me and
more like he's infatuated.
But if I point that out to him,
he's just going to try harder,
which will make it even harder to
figure out what he's thinkin'.
It's easier for me if he just keeps
acting like a psycho... I think.
Oh, dear, that sounds like a lot of trouble.
And to think the first person who
confessed to you was Kirishima-kun...
Quit the pickle.
Hey, it's not my fault!
Have you ever talked to Kirishima-kun
about his old girlfriends before?
I know that he fools around, but...
We usually only talk about food
or current events, so not really.
Wow, you skipped the dating phase and went
straight to acting like an old retired couple?
You don't know whether or not you're coming
back to Osaka or staying in Tokyo,
and you don't know if he
really likes you or not...
You probably want to start
setting things straight.
If the former's true, even coming
home won't mean an end of trouble.
The first semester has come to an end,
and summer vacation will begin tomorrow...
Is it obsession or love? And how
the hell do I figure that out?!
Hey, do you wanna join us?
P-Pardon us!
Older students showin'
me that kinda respect...
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Yoshino. Let's head home.
What were you talking about?
The campus is going to be open over summer,
so we were discussing who
would end up with guide duty.
Looking after visitors falls under the
disciplinary committee's responsibilities.
And that means me.
You?! Discipline?!
Yeah.
Is that some kinda joke?!
All you do is flaunt the rules!
I might break the law, but generally
speaking, I obey school rules.
Most students tend to
break the latter, not the former!
Gotta be honest, I thought maybe
those girls were asking you out.
Of course not. I got a few approaches
when I was a first-year,
but since I turned them all down,
they just assume that I'll do it again,
so they've stopped trying.
You don't have any guy friends, do ya?
What makes you say that?
Because if I was a guy, and
I heard that, I'd be pissed.
You're all I really need anyway, Yoshino.
You mean to tell me I fill the
role of guy friends for you?
I think so, yeah.
You're my first friend, after all.
But all we talk about is
food and current events!
But you're the only one I
talk to about that stuff.
Girls just talk even if I
don't pay attention to them.
You're the only one I actually
have conversations with
about stuff like food and news.
You realize...
that makes it sound like you intend on
marrying the first friend you've ever made...
You know, you're right. It does.
I-I think this goes beyond
like or obsession...
Does he even understand what it means to
be romantically interested in someone?
Forget how he acted with
his old girlfriends...
If I'm not even being considered
as the same kind of thing,
what exactly have I been risking
my life for this whole time?
What a mess...
I'd Rather You Hate Me than Not Care
Part One
Over there...
Is that Shiota Nao?
Didn't she used to be a child actress?
And then she retired because her
parents moved to America for work?
Last year, she won a beauty
contest at Seitoku U.
And she was a student anchor
on a satellite news show!
She's so damn cute!
I guess she's back in Japan.
Nao! Sorry about the wait.
I didn't meant to, but I was
talking with the director
from that commercial I filmed recently
and ended up running late.
Thanks.
When I mentioned you, Nao,
he was interested in meeting you.
Really? Maybe I should say hi.
Oh, definitely! You're gonna be working
in showbiz again starting next year.
Show business? I'm going
to be an office worker!
You're going to be a newscaster on a major
network! That's not an office worker.
You're basically performing.
Huh?
Is that Ozu-kun?
You used to go out with him, right, Nao?
Uh, yeah...
Why'd you break up? He's hot!
When he found out I was going
to be in a beauty contest,
he said, "I didn't know you
were so attention-hungry."
What, really? Good thing you dumped him!
That's gotta be annoying, considering
you're nothing like that, Nao.
I only entered because one of
the organizers begged me to.
What a load of crap.
I know that they all secretly
think I'm a schemer.
But what's wrong with that?
All I'm doing is putting in more effort
than most to get people to like me.
And at the end of the day, I'm the
most successful one in our group.
I get worried about how much of an
airhead you can be sometimes, Nao-chan.
Don't get involved with
anyone dangerous, okay?
Just imagine her ending
up with a scary guy...
Y'know, like that guy over there.
Isn't that Kirishima-kun?
I haven't seen him in a while.
Kirishima...?
There's all kinds of weird rumors about him.
Oh, right.
Remember that girl who was planning to be
an actress and started doing pin-up shoots?
She ended up starring in some
porn before going missing.
And before she went missing, a friend
of hers saw her around Kirishima-kun.
Well, you hear stories
like that all the time...
I've only talked to Kirishima-kun a few times.
I don't know him too well.
Good to see you again.
Oh, good to see you!
We were just talking about how we
hadn't seen you around lately.
Really? I've seen you plenty, though.
You were just in that commercial for
the wedding venue, right, Sara-chan?
Oh, wow, I'm impressed you noticed!
Oh, I think this is your
first time meeting her.
She won a beauty contest for her college.
Yeah, I know.
She keeps really busy.
I saw her pop up on social
media just the other day.
You know all about her, then!
Come to think of it,
you're gonna be working some big
event in Osaka soon, right, Nao?
Y-Yeah...
Huh, that's impressive.
Maybe I should attend,
if my schedule's open.
Nobody knows.
Nao, you went to Minatoyama
Elementary School, right?
I heard there was some
kind of big, violent incident there.
And it was even covered up.
Isn't that crazy?
Nao, do you know Kirishima-kun?
Should I introduce you?
Y'know... I've known about
you for a long time now.
You're a yakuza's grandson, aren't you?
It was only for the short time I came back
to Japan during summer vacation, but...
I was in his bed basically every day.
Even though I knew how dangerous he was.
It's been a while.
It has.
Um... sorry about earlier.
It's fine. I was pretending
I didn't know you, too.
That was three years ago, after all.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Sorry to put you out like this.
Nao-chan, you've really changed.
I seem to remember you being more
the type to speak your mind.
You might be right.
When you live overseas, you kinda
have to speak your mind more often,
but in Japan it makes me stand out.
Don't try too hard to fit in, okay?
Yeah, I know. Thanks.
Oh, hang on, I wanted to give you something.
This might not be a great use of
someone else's business card...
But I wrote my contact
info on the back of it.
Let me know if you need anything. Bye now.
Whoa, isn't this—?
Man, he has crazy connections.
Is Kirishima back?
I can't see anything.
Tsubaki
Actually, Yoshino-chan, putting exes aside,
do you even know how Kirishima-kun
spends his time?
Hello?
Hey, Kirishima?
I was wondering if you were back.
Well, I am. What's up?
Remember how I mentioned
going home to Osaka for Bon?
But when I thought about the holiday rush,
I figure maybe August 7th or 8th would
be a better time to grab tickets.
If you're busy then,
you can always come in later.
Does that work?
It's not... exactly a problem.
But is it possible we could
maybe head there in July?
I don't mind, but...
If you're too busy, I can always
just pop over and then come back, right?
Shiota Nao
I'm going to be in Osaka for three days
starting July 30th participating in the
#SummerGroove festival for the
cosmetics brand #Joli. The official
announcement will be for the
#JoliCanvasContest Grand Prix.
There's going to be online voting too.
Don't be silly. I wouldn't dream of it.
I'm looking forward to it, actually.
Can't wait to go to Osaka.
Man, it's hot...
It's only been three months,
but it feels like it's been forever.
I know I asked before, but considering
I've got graves to visit,
what are you going to do in the meantime?
Grandpa won't be home until August, either.
Don't worry. I'll just wander around a bit.
I haven't been to Osaka much before.
What, really?
Well, in terms of looks and language, you
seem like a nice, well-bred boy from Tokyo.
So I'm begging you, even if someone
starts shit, restrain yourself.
There's no telling what kinda trouble
you could get into down here!
Just stay where I can keep
an eye on you. Got it?
That almost sounds like
you care about me.
Would you mind repeating it?
Get serious!
Well, whatever.
For now, we'll stop at Umeda, and I guess we
can pick up some lunch while we're there.
What are you in the mood for?
I'm picky about how pork buns smell, so
I tend to buy them close to the house,
and the best okonomiyaki place
I know is near the house too.
Well... whatever you
prefer is fine, Yoshino.
Okonomiyaki it is, then!
I'm craving the sauce.
We can grab rice and grilled squid
at the Hanshin Department Store.
Might as well drop by Hankyu too!
Here we are! Man, it really
is quite a trip from Tokyo.
Let's grab a cab. And then we can
get the okonomiyaki on the way.
You're still not done shopping?
Finally feels like I'm home!
Sorry for draggin' you around like this.
No, it's totally fine.
If you're having a good time,
then so am I, Yoshino.
And it feels like a long time
since I last saw you smile.
You might be cute when you're mad,
but at the end of the day you
look your best when you smile.
There you go again, shamelessly
spoutin' nonsense like that...
Excuse me, driver!
Hey, you! What're you doing out here?!
I mean... eating takoyaki?
In the middle of the blazin' sun,
I oughta point out...
But that's not my point!
What about your classes?
I finished mine for today.
Liar!
Well, I'm here to pick you up, Yoshino-san.
I figured you'd come here for lunch
first thing after getting back.
Damn, man. I didn't even say
anythin' to tip you off...
Yoshino, what about the cab?
Hey there.
Crap, I told him not to pick a
fight even if someone gets on him,
but I didn't think that the most likely
culprit would be at the damn house!
Hey, Kirishima, unload the bags!
I'll pay the fare.
Don't drop yer ashes in front of my shop.
You've been smokin' nonstop.
That's 'cuz it's my shop,
dummy, so I get to.
Granny! It's been so long!
Well! If it ain't Yoshino-chan!
How you been?
Whoa, hang on!
Who's this handsome fella? Your boyfriend?
No, no, no!
Well, damn! He's certainly fine.
Has the "young actor" look.
Thank you very much.
Where's he from? One of
the boss's younger guys?
I'm a classmate of Yoshino-san's.
I came from Tokyo.
From Tokyo?!
That'd explain how sharp you look!
Huh, I had him pegged for
your new sugar baby!
We ain't got that kind of money!
Tell me about it. I figure a young fella
like this would probably turn us down,
no matter what price we were offering!
I don't agree. I'd gladly let ladies
as beautiful as you take care of me.
Keep talkin'...
Did you hear that?!
He definitely ain't from Osaka!
Shoma! You're handsome too,
so maybe you oughta learn some
lessons about how to talk!
Shaddup, fool.
Ain't seen someone as
hot as that in a while.
Sweetie, here's some allowance
from yours truly.
Go and buy yourself a drink.
Hey! You seriously don't need to do that!
It's fine, it's fine!
You just got paid for being handsome.
Should I really keep it?
They're already gone, so you might as well.
We can grab a few roast cabbages
with it on the way to the house.
I am exhausted...
It's never as fun to travel
when it's for work.
Nao, you're gonna show up for
your circle's excursion, right?
Some kinda volunteer thing?
Oh, right, but I'm really
just dropping by to say hi.
Come to think of it, have
you seen Ozu-kun lately?
Weren't you in the same circle as him?
And do you remember what I told you?
Ever since that party, he's
been keeping in touch with me.
Yeah, I think he's going to be attending
the volunteer thing in Kansai.
Okay. I guess that's fine...
Did something happen?
I didn't know that he was the son
of an exec at Embrace Productions.
Not only that, but his mother is that
freelance TV announcer, Kondo Sakiko!
She's a big deal! Did you know?
We only went out for about
three months, so no.
Obviously, I knew that.
It might've been the biggest
reason I started dating him.
Well, this is just a rumor,
but I heard some students from the university
tried to drag one of their models to a hotel.
The cops ended up getting involved.
Since it involved Embrace, I wondered
if he was a friend of Ozu-kun's.
Did that really happen?
Since he's rich, and probably knows all
kinds of girls, I bet guys try to use him.
So I was thinking, if
you had heard from him,
that he might have been trying to
introduce you to somebody.
I wonder how likely that is...
Eh, you can just ignore it then.
Or maybe get a new boyfriend?
I have a friend who, whenever a
weirdo starts following her around,
gets with a tough-looking guy,
and then the problem clears right up.
Let me know if you need anything.
Welcome back!
Hey, it's good to be back.
What's wrong? Come on inside.
Pardon the intrusion.
It's nice to meet you all.
My name is Miyama Kirishima.
I'll be staying with you for a while.
Oh, we've heard about you.
Likewise, it's nice to have you with us.
Shoma, throw these groceries
in the fridge, would you?
Sure.
Let's head to my room for now.
So that's Boss Miyama's grandson...
And we're really lettin'
him stay in the house?
I mean... If the boss says it's
fine, then it's fine, right?
Ugh, it's so hot.
Just put the stuff down and then
sit on the bed or wherever.
I guess we'll eat lunch in
here or maybe the guest room.
When Grandpa's around, we
have huge meals every day,
so we'll be eating with a buncha other
people whether we like it or not.
What should we do for dinner?
You gonna sit?
Is there something weird about the room?
No. It's just really nice.
You think? Seems pretty normal to me.
Is this hand-made?
Oh, those?
I got into crafts in grade school
and ended up makin' a buncha stuff.
Not much of it was good.
It's cute. And pretty well-made.
You can keep it if you want.
Eh, you probably don't
need that ancient thing!
I can really keep it?
Sure, that's fine.
Thank you.
In that case, maybe a newer one—
Yoshino-san!
What's up?
There were some frozen rice cakes in the
groceries. What should I do with 'em?
Sorry, I gotta head downstairs.
This is Shiota Nao.
Do you remember me?
I was really surprised to see
you again after such a long time!
Thank you for coming by to say hi.
We didn't get to talk much
Man, I haven't had kushikatsu in a while.
It was good, but what the hell
is a kushikatsu sampler plate?
It was good, so I don't care.
You never care as long as
it fills your stomach.
I could go for more.
What the hell is going on with your guts?
Oh, Kirishima, how'd you
like it? Good stuff?
Yeah, of course.
Really! That's a relief.
This is exhausting.
Well, I should get going.
Wait, why?
I booked a room at a nearby hotel.
I'll come by the house tomorrow morning.
You got a hotel room?!
You could just stay at the house!
No, that's probably not a good idea.
But you left your bags there...
I had my necessities sent
down from Tokyo already.
Well, I'm gonna go. Please
look after Yoshino.
And Yoshino, I'll see you tomorrow.
Uh, okay, see you tomorrow.
Is he always like that?
Well, most of the time, yeah.
Why?
You oughta talk to him more.
Talk to him?
Guy like that, you're better off
knowing exactly what he's up to.
There's no telling what he might pull.
What are you talking about?
If you're really getting
the runaround from him,
you seem to be a actin' a little
too relaxed... or maybe careless.
I mean... if he don't wanna talk
about himself, I'm not gonna ask,
and I don't see how that's being careless.
I guess you're right.
Now that I think about it,
it probably don't matter.
Hey! Don't try and buy that
while I'm distracted!
If you want that, you gotta put this back!
Tsubaki said something similar.
I guess it's worth a shot.
Don't worry. I'm not a yakuza.
Kirishima-kun, why are you here in Osaka?
I wanted to see you, Nao.
Come on! I'm being serious.
Well, so am I.
Why did you contact me, Nao?
Did something happen?
Not really...
I just kind of wanted to.
Are you going to be in Osaka tomorrow, too?
I'll be here for a while.
Although I was thinking of heading
over to Kyoto tomorrow.
For a date with your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
But I do have someone I think I like.
You really are sketchy, Kirishima-kun.
You've got me there.
I'm gonna take a shower.
One notification